so with that um carl if you're here
hopefully you're here
uh please feel free to uh unmute
yourself and uh and share your screen
welcome thank you very much thank you
for another introduction
let me share my screen and then
great well it's a great pleasure to be
here and also nice to see so many
so many old friends as well that's a
perverse gift of covid
and i was torn um
about what to talk about over the next
half hour
between looking at markov blankets as
one way of studying emergentism
and embodiment when the internal states
synchronize with the external states
or focusing on the intelligence part of
embodied intelligence but i've elected
to go for the intelligence part and pick
up
on um one of the themes that the first
keynote um uh introduced this notion of
intrinsic motivation
and a theme which came back
a number of times particularly in in
gentani's and and andy clark's uh
presentations the you know the notion of
planning and temporal depth and an
understanding
of the imperatives for um behavior
and active engagement with the world
that looks into the future so i'm going
to
focus on the intelligence bit of
embodied intelligence
and i'm going to cast that in terms of
self-evidencing
briefly rehearse what i mean by that in
terms of normative models of action and
perception and possibly
uh consciousness and cognition um
how it relates to or how self-evidencing
um
brings to the table some things that
would be useful for understanding
embodiment in artificial intelligence
and then
if we have time um just use a
um a toy simulation just to unpack
how the principles work and some of the
fundaments of
the behavior that ensues so i'm taking
my lead
from the notion that all we need to
know in terms of explaining and
understanding
self-organized behavior of a sentient
and possibly intelligent
sword um is that everything uh
in our brains or in our body
and in particular those bits of the body
that change the way that the brain and
the body
samples its its sensorium and its echo
niche
everything is just in the service of
maximizing
the evidence for a artifact
or a creatures generative model of its
world
m here so i'm just articulating that
mathematically
everything is in the service of
maximizing probability of some
observable outcomes some sensed outcomes
given a model of those outcomes and i'm
just um
portraying here a number of different
takes on that that would depend upon
your commitments and your training you
could um
interpret the log of the probability of
those outcomes
that you're trying to solicit or
behave in a way to maximize the
probability of
of those outcomes being elicited as
value the valuable
outcomes and you could look at that from
the point of view of reinforcement
learning optimal control
theory or indeed if you're an economist
expected utility theory
i've cast value um in terms of a
negative potential um that is in fact
the self information in information
theory so uh sometimes referred to as
surprise
or surprise and that's nice because if
we're trying to maximize value or have a
normative take on
value maximization then what we're also
saying is that we also have an
information theoretic
understanding of the imperatives that um
are convinced by self-evidencing in
terms of uh
principles of minimum redundancy or
maximum efficiency and indeed the free
energy principles so
um just noting that the free energy that
some people have mentioned
provides a bound on surprise or value
when cast in this way in turn that is
also nice because the
time average of surprisal or
self-information is entropy
so what we're saying is in
self-evidencing then we are
just trying to
resist the dispersion uh according to
the second law
uh which of course is the holy grail of
self-organization particularly in things
like cybernetics and synergetics
of course if you're a physiologist it's
just homeostasis keeping
physiological outcomes or observable
states of the body
within viable physiological bounds i'm
going to
actually take another perspective though
on this quantity
which is the statistician's perspective
name of the probability of some
outcomes or observables given a model
constituting the marginal likelihood
of that model or the model evidence and
then one can spin off the base in brain
hypothesis evidence accumulation
predictive coding and the like so that's
where i'm coming from um i want to now
just drill down on what that means
mathematically and it's related
to a couple of things that we've already
been talking about so why
self-evidencing well
this this um quantity um constitutes the
sort of
you know the core part of this free
energy
in machine learning this is known as an
evidence lower bound
why well because there's a bound here
which can never be less than
zero which means that if i maximize f
i am necessarily maximizing a bound on
the log evidence hence
self-evidencing um this quantity
is going to be interesting later on but
let me just focus in the first instance
of why
it will be useful from the point of view
of say
artificial intelligence um to maximize
the evidence for a model of the world
and implicit in having a model
is an explainability so the
quantity the objective function that i'm
trying to optimize
is an explicit functional of a model
that renders it
inherently explainable so we have a
transparency and expandability and
indeed interpretability
for free that leads on to something
quite important which is optimal
bayesian design
um and of course the interpretation of
self-evidencing in terms
of a bayesian brain or a prediction
machine
a constructive organ making inferences
about its environment
um and of course when you embody or put
that in
in an active context we have um a degree
of
self-assembly autophasis and
self-teaching
or autodidactic um capacitors
which leads to a principled way of
understanding data foraging
and epistemics and possibly animal or
generalized artificial intelligence but
i want to just rearrange that equation
which is the way that somebody machine
learning might understand
um this free energy bound um
i'm just moving the terms around just to
express it in a way that a statistician
would be more familiar with it which is
basically
the imperative to maximize the accuracy
for your
explanations or predictions of sensed
outcomes
whilst at the same time minimizing the
complexity where the complexity
is the degree of belief updating or the
amount you have to change your mind
in relation to new data the degrees of
freedom you're using up
in terms of providing an accurate
explanation
and i'm going on about that because i
was intrigued by the discussion
of complexity either in the brain or in
the body and simplexity and the like
and this is a central notion in terms of
self-evidencing where
if not um most of but certainly a
substantial part of the drives to
maximize this evidence lower bound is in
getting the simplest most parsimonious
explanations
implicit in your generative model um
that you can so that's just across the
statement of occam's principle and you
see that emerging in structure function
relationships in terms of things like
modular factorizations in computers or
indeed the brain where it's known as
functional specialization
efficient coding it also um
[Music]
provides an interesting um take on
bounded rationality that
you know it's not a question of just
being rational and very accurate
it's a way it's a special kind and
optimal
maximum evidence way of being rational
where you're trying to find the simplest
explanations so it easily accommodates
the notion of heuristics
via prize inherent in the genitive model
namely
the probability of some states of
affairs in the world generating
uh these outcomes here um it also
practically
means that when the artifact
is behaving
in an optimal way in relation to
free energy or marginal likelihood
there's some simple physics which says
it should be doing it
in the most thermodynamically efficient
way so you can invoke
the jninski equality and landauer's
principle to say that
if you've got the right solution or your
artifact
is self-evidencing optimally then it
will be
consuming the least amount of
electricity it will be as small and as
simple as possible
and so that's the basic if you like
motivations
for self-evidencing cast in terms of
maximizing model evidence
or marginal likelihood what i want to do
though is ask
what would that look like if i had to
choose how to use my body
to maximize the free energy in the
future
and essentially what i'm going to be
saying is that
if i condition the outcomes
yet to be observed on some plan
then accuracy and complexity translate
into two things which
yeah which we will all immediately
recognize
basically um they're going to translate
into
an optimal design and an optimum
decision making
so what the story i'm telling here is
that self evidencing just
is a mixture of base optimal design
in the way that we go and solicit
evidence from the world
evidence for our own existence for our
generative model
under pry beliefs about the kind of
thing that i am
so here in this instance um the
base optimality of is of a decision
theoretics or that if i choose to do
this
then the outcomes are going to be close
to my prior beliefs about the kind of
outcomes
a thing like me will expect to encounter
so i'm just going to briefly rehearse
that story
um by comparing and contrasting
um conventional rl like approaches to
optimality versus this more general
self-evidencing approach
and and i normally start this this
lecture
um by asking you to imagine that you're
a bird of prey and you're hungry
and then i asked the audience normally
um what are you going to do
and they normally say quite correctly
i'm going to search and fly around until
i find my
prey and then i'm going to eat my prey
and in that answer
there is buried um an important
or several important takes on
the kind of functions or functionals
that you would use to try and describe
good behavior so we could either
assume the existence of a value function
of some
states of the world that
are contingent upon some action or
control variable you
here and if this value function
of states of the world existed then i
could
uh optimize the value by selecting
the best state action policy pi policy
by selecting the action u for every
given state
that maximize this value function and
this is known as the
optimality principle um
however just in saying i'm gonna search
for my food before i eat it
you're saying something quite profound
because searching
is a action that resolves uncertainty
and uncertainty is an attribute of a
probabilistic or a bayesian belief
and therefore the thing that you are
optimizing
can't be a function of unknown states
for the world
it has to be a function of beliefs about
states of the world so in
in the sort of bayesian um
interpretation
i'm denoting posterior or approximate
posterior beliefs about states of the
world by q
so what we're saying is optimal action
depends not upon states of the world but
on beliefs abound states of the world
and we get this sort of functional form
here
the other thing um that the sort of
um the owl example um
shows is that the order matters
it matters whether i first of all
search for my prey and then eat it or
try to eat it and then search for it
which means that there does not exist an
optimal state
action um policy but more
an optimal sequence of behaviors
given what i currently believe about the
state of the world at this point in time
and we can articulate that in terms
of a path or a time integral of this um
quantity which is in fact going to be um
an expected free energy that andy
and a number of other people have
already mentioned um
leading us to an optimization
of a time integral of an energy function
which in physics is an
action and i'm phrasing it like that
because
what we've basically got here is a
choice between the bellman optimality
principle
that would seem things like optimal
control theory or dynamic processing
deep reinforcement learning basic
decision theory
on one hand or on the other hand we have
hamilton's principle of released action
um or station reactions more strictly
that is exemplified by things like
active inference and subsumes things
like artificial curiosity and intrinsic
motivation
that i'm going to cast in terms of
optimal bayesian design that optimally
resolves uncertainty about
my hypotheses about how my body works
and how the world works
it also entails sequential policy
optimization
and the distinction between observations
of a certain world and partially
observed
worlds so here's the basic
architecture that one has in mind when
invoking and we've seen not some lovely
examples
of this for example giantani's um
um illustration this morning um
so you know the basic theme um
the embodiment gets into the act here in
terms of this sort of reciprocal
engagement this circular
causal link between the inside and the
outside
that andy was talking about
mathematically what what
one way in which one can describe this
is that you get these outcomes supplied
by the environment
you use these outcomes to maximize a
functional of those
outcomes and your beliefs under a
genetic model about states
causing those outcomes and to form
posterior beliefs about states of the
world out there
you then use these to roll out
effectively into the future
under a number of potential policies so
this is
exactly the poise over possible actions
or an
action space the action space here is
explicitly
encoded in terms of sequences of
actions or moves on the world denoted by
pi
and each pi you can roll out and
estimate the expected free energy which
i've here decompose into risk and
ambiguity
and we'll drill down in that onto in
that
in the next slide at the moment we just
need to know now we've got a way of
scoring
each way forward each one of these
possible action
um possible policies possible plans
can be scored in relation to our beliefs
about the kinds of things that we
expect to encounter and the kinds of
things that we do with our bodies
and that score can then be used to find
the most likely
policy and with selected action from
that
belief about the most likely policy it
changes states in the world the world
supplies a new outcome and uh off we go
again
in this perception action-like cycle
that has this planning and policy
selection
um as an integral part of it um so
this is the the bit that sort of um
links
the notion of simplexity and complexity
and
to the um more prospective
aspects of action and
planning so what i've done here
is rewrite down the the evidence lower
bound
the free energy here in terms of
accuracy and complexity
and remember the complexities is the
difference between your posteriors and
your priors the
amount you've had to change your mind
which is the energy
hungry part of it and the accuracy
here and just by moving the terms around
uh we can
reconstitute or recover uh the ex the
expression
that lends its um elbow acronym the
evidence lower bound because this
quantity
um is always greater than zero and
here's the expected value has a very
very similar form the only difference is
that we're now conditioning upon some
possible action or possible sequence of
actions
and interestingly what happens now is of
course you don't have the observations
that would be used to evaluate the free
energy because they are now random
variables in the future
so you now have to take your expectation
over
the prediction of the outcomes
in the future given i'm going to do that
and hence expected free energy
but the form is the same and i like this
because it's really quite revealing so
the complexity becomes risk the accuracy
becomes on the negative accuracy becomes
ambiguity
which means that we're going to choose
those things if we
are choosing those things that maximize
expected free energy
in the future we are necessarily going
to be minimizing our risk and minimizing
our ambiguity and i'll explain what that
means in a second
or we can carve up this expected free
energy in another way
in terms of the intrinsic and the
extrinsic value
and this is the intrinsic motivation so
we have
basically um both the complexity
and the intrinsic motivation um or the
expected complexity and intrinsic
motivation
as different ways of carving up this
underlying
imperative for self-evidencing but
self-evidencing
where you're maximizing the expected
evidence in the future given a
particular action
just to unpack this a little bit for
those people in
different fields if i ignore the
extrinsic value at the moment and by
which i mean
i've got some prior beliefs about the
kind of outcomes that i
as a creature will expect to encounter
if i have no particular preferences
prior preferences then we're just left
with this thing here which is the
expected evidence bound
and this quantity here is is just the
difference
in my posterior beliefs with and without
observations that i would get if i
pursued this policy
and of course this is um the basis of
the mutual information between the
consequences and their causes
states here and that will be expected
under that particular policy
if you do visual search or active
sensing active vision
um then you may recognize this as the
expected base in surprise basically
the amount of information the epistemic
affordance
attributed or afforded by this
particular policy
the reduction in certainty about states
of affairs in the world out there
in the future um given observations
um and evidence for those states um uh
in the future if
i committed to that particular policy
um if i take uncertainty
of the various kinds off the table we're
actually going to get back to
reinforcement learning or expected
utility but let me just do that
carefully
let's first of all assume that we've got
a simple world in which we can
sense the states of the world so we
remove the uncertainty about
um that's inherent in the partially
observed
aspects of certain models so that
we magically our outcomes now become the
hidden states
of of the world we can see everything in
this instance the s's become the o's
um and we're just left then the
ambiguity goes where there is no more
ambiguity in the world we know exactly
what's going on
um and that just leaves the risk so what
is a risk well it's the
against the kl divergence between what i
expect to happen under this policy
and my prior preferences so when i
minimize
risk what i'm doing is i'm choosing
those policies that will lead to states
of the world
or their outcomes that a priori i prefer
so i'm trying to minimize
the degree of divergence or difference
between again
posteriors about future outcomes and
price over future outcomes
so very very closely related to
complexity the complexity cost
but now we're talking about the future
and
if i remove the final kind of
uncertainty from
the table um what we're left with
is effectively um and the final kind of
uncertainty is that the
um the uncertainty due to different
actions
relative uncertainty just disappears i'm
just left with this thing here which um
i set up in the first slide as being
really a version
of um um expected utility theory where
um the the um expected or extrinsic
value
is just the expected value or the log
probability of preferred outcomes under
what i anticipate
uh to ensure given a particular um
given all um policies or actions here
so what we've done here is
is derive from the simple notion
of self-evidencing the service of
garnering evidence for your own
existence
as implied by your model your embodied
model
of the world and carving it up into
two different aspects of bayesian good
behavior
first of all um i'm going to um
commit to those behaviors that would um
um or choices that have the greatest
expected value
and in in statistics that's known as
making bayes optimal decisions under
some loss function but here we're
casting
the loss function of the utility
function uh
in terms of a prior preference and then
which is adding to that effectively the
information
gain um that ensues from pursuing a
particular policy and together
they constitute the expected free energy
or the expected
evidence uh afforded by a particular
policy
so i'm going to close now just by very
quickly taking you through some
uh embarrassingly simple simulations and
we looked at the beautiful simulations
uh this morning uh um we we are
nowhere near and uh able to uh scale up
to that level of sophistication however
i think they're still illuminating um um
you know in the sense that there's a
certain simplicity in
you know in what i'm saying even though
some of the maths may look a bit
complicated
and i'm not going to go through this in
any detail i want to show you the
the the kind of behavior the sort of
behavior
um that is mandated under this
um optimization of expected free energy
we normally use markov decision
processes sort of discrete
state space models of a world
[Music]
graphically cast in terms of transitions
from one state to the next point in time
generating outcomes the likelihood
mapping
where the transitions are dependent upon
a policy uh be use your code
encoding the um the probability
transitions
and then we have interesting um well the
policy clearly depends on the prior
preferences included by this
preference or cost function here um
we also have in many of the simulations
uh
um the precision of our beliefs about
policies and i just mentioned that
because that's
the w in john's talk that sort of tunes
the hierarchical depth or the
ability to learn versus to teach uh
depending upon
the confidence that a priori you place
in
your uh your um inactive policies
um when interrogating or queering uh
querying the row
the world a couple of hyper parameters
about initial states
and when we plug this very generic um
form for the generative model into
standard elbow or free
energy optimization schemes we get a a
series of belief
updating uh equations that look very
much like what the brain does and indeed
we know that because
of all the um all the simulations and
interpretations process theories that
we've already
um uh witnessed um this morning and in
the literature
um so you know there aren't many
unknowns here we just don't
we don't know about the state of the
world we don't know what we're doing and
we don't know how confident we are
in what we're doing um we actually also
don't know
um the parameters of the of the of the
model itself
um um you know the the likelihood
mappings and the
uh the transition matrices so those can
be learned
um so we just have perception which is
resolving uncertainty or inferring
states of the world
policies select policy selection so
having the right poise if that's correct
abuse of and its philosophical term on
the
space or possible actions and and
also having a um a kind of second order
belief about the
the our beliefs about those actions in
terms of the confidence or the precision
that incidentally looks as if it's
encoded by dopamine in
human brains um then we have learning of
the unknown
structure of the world um that would be
a particularly interesting
from the point of view of the sort of
you know the embodiment part of this
equation
and then action selection is selecting
an action from my beliefs about what i
do
and when i simulate that and i'm going
to simulate that
um by applying those equations to a
little mouse
who um can um has to
solicit a baited reward from the right
or the left
um arms uh it's only um
it only has two moves and has to stay in
one or the other arm
once committing to one of those arms but
it has a choice of
using up one of its moves to go and get
an instructional cue
that will tell it um definitively
whether the
reward is there or there so this little
rat has the choice of taking a gamble uh
and it could be 50 percent correct and
staying there
um or spending one of its um
exploitative moves in an exploratory
sense
to go resolve uncertainty about the
world and then go and secure
the um the cheese
and and of course this is set up this
sort of two-step paradigm is set up just
to demonstrate
even though the expected utility of both
policies um is identical uh on
average um the the self-evidencing
uh creature will clearly go and resolve
its uncertainty
responding to the epistemic affordance
of the intrinsic motivation
go and get the cue and then uh go and
enjoy and exploit
it's it's um it's knowledge um
um by going to the the arm
that is baited and indeed that's what
the agent does but what this simulation
um is showing is is a systematic and
principled and completely non-determined
uh non-um
stochastic this is a deterministic
optimization of expected free energy
which means that if you actually
introduce a predictability and a
structure and a consistency
uh to the world which we've done here
just by leaving the reward
on the left arm perpetually after the
first couple of moves
then the creature the the rat
will come to learn this and therefore
the
salience or the novelty of the
uncertainty resolving q
slowly wanes and
there is no uncertainty after a while
because the rat knows that the reward is
over
on the side and therefore the epistemic
affordance the
um the explorative dry's intrinsic
motivation for going to
the condition stimulus or the
instructional cue
starts to disappear and at some point
when the intrinsic and the extrinsic
well well the intrinsic value of
motivation
falls below the pragmatic
or the extrinsic value it'll just switch
to a different kind of behavior
and this is incredibly systematic and
you see this in many many simulations
and indeed in real world uh situations
where you know
your first imperative is to resolve
uncertainty
about this particular world this
eco-niche
this body um and when you've done that
you start
to then turn to your prior preferences
um because there's no more uncertainty
to hoover up
um so by move 20 the rat just goes
straight
there quite happily and will do so
forever if nothing else changes
this is the final slide and um i've got
30 seconds left um so um
i put this here just to remind myself
um about that initial um
ambivalence of about whether to talk
about sort of uh the emergence of
life-like
uh behavior um from first principles or
whether to talk about the sort of
the mechanics of planning and uh deep
charging models
of my own action um it would be nice to
to to actually connect the two
perspectives um
and i'm just putting this up as an
outstanding challenge
uh and the framing which i think that
challenge can be met
um i won't go into this but other than
to if anybody's interested
provide a sort of starting point for
discussion so here's what we've just
been basically saying
we can understand the right kinds of
behavior
in terms of selecting
the right possible actions and what are
the right ones whether
they're the ones that underwrite our
self-evidencing that minimize risk and
ambiguity
and they have this functional form
there's another way of understanding
the universe in terms of um
non-equilibrium steady states that are
normally described in terms of integral
fluctuation theorems if you did
chemistry or
or physics and they have
um a very similar structure in terms of
articulating
the probabilistic development of um
states and and and outcomes consequences
of
upon different states um
in terms of chaos divergences to provide
bound
or inequalities underwrite much of
statistical thermodynamics
interestingly you can use the integral
fluctuation theorems
to derive this if you make one
particular assumption or commitment one
small move here
and all i'll say about this is it hasn't
actually been done yet
but it does involve some probabilistic
relationship about between the
probability
of a path of action into the future and
the ambiguity or the um the negative
um the negative entropy of outcomes
given given their causes um so again
linking action and uncertainty you know
in an intimate way which may be the key
for
uh understanding the kinds of systems
eye creatures like us
that distinguish ourselves from things
like viruses or
other self-organizing systems that don't
plan
anyway um i'll leave the last word with
einstein everything should be made as
simple as possible
but not simpler and all that remains is
for me to thank
uh those people whose ideas i've been
talking about of course
thank you for your attention thank you
very much indeed i'll stop my sharing
thank you very much carl i i'm sure the
348 participants if they could they
would unmute and
join me in thanking you there's a couple
questions arriving
in the discord um so before we we get to
uh one or two questions
um i just like to ask the organizers if
they could help connect professor
fristen with
the discord if if he's not there already
there's a question from dana damian
beautiful theory
thank you um does this theory also
explain the emergence of belief in the
first place
um in an elemental way
yes um so that would be part of the
story that
i couldn't tell so um if you just take
any um system that has self-organized
some kind of non-equilibrium steady
state so it persists there are
recognizable characteristics and then
and then you partition that system into
inside states that constitute the inside
of a system and the
environment and then they're enshrouded
by blanket states this is a markov
blanket
partition then you can
use the necessary properties of
non-equilibrium steady states solving
the density dynamics to show that there
is an information geometry
where the physical inside states
come to parameterize bayesian or
probabilistic beliefs about the outside
states
and that licenses then an information
geometry which is
a geometry of belief state so if you
if you permit me to interpret beliefs as
bayesian or probabilistic beliefs
conditional probability distributions
then mathematically you're saying is
there an information geometry there
and what i would say yes there is under
the condition you've organized to a
non-equilibrium steady state
great thank you again more questions
arriving there's a question here in zoom
chat from
from andy um if minimizing expected free
energy delivers simple planning
what delivers deliberate deliberate
planning
that seems different yet related
um i think the distinction is is a very
subtle one
um and um we don't have time to
to get into it because it is a really
interesting question so notice that
um i was talking um i was just carving
this um functional this sort of expected
free energy model evidence into two bits
that literally decompose because we're
in long space into sort of an
information gain effectively
and a you know a pragmatic or
um expected utility term that added
that that would be could be resolved
independently
so you could argue well look yeah that's
fine
but that's not really resolving
uncertainty about what matters to me in
relation to my prior preferences
yeah so yeah i'm just resolving all
uncertainty irrespective of
you know what what i actually think i
should be uh the
kinds of things i'm going to i'm going
to solicit
so if andy's asking that question to ask
well when does it get more interesting
one could algorithmically say well you
have to move to sophisticated inference
where you actually have to
um instead of just resolving uncertainty
you have to actually encode
what would i believe if i knew that and
what would those new beliefs mean
as i work towards my preferences it's
not difficult to do it's basically a
probabilistic generalization of the
uh the bellman recursion however
i'd actually say you probably don't need
to do that because remember
although these two bits of the
the good ways to choose your policies
are literally separable they're linearly
separable in log space
which means you're actually multiplying
so what you are saying in probably in
terms of probabilities
i am choosing those um policies that
have the greatest epistemic affordance
given that they afford um outcomes that
i
prefer so i think there's actually built
in for free a certain sort of
deliberation there in the sense that
you're conditioned upon
resolving uncertainty there has to be an
aspiration to the goals that are written
into
the prior preferences great thank you um
we have some time for discussion at the
end of the plenary session so i'm going
to
uh use my host privileges here and ask
you one last question
um from discord um how does free energy
deal with uh groups of agents and a
common belief among the group
will it promote agreeing uh with the
group over further exploration of the
environment
yeah yes it does it promotes cooperation
and generalized synchrony so
mathematically you know that that
generalized synchrony
basically affords a predictability of
two agents in a diet or
in fact a multi-agent context so if the
whole game is to minimize surprise
then the best solution is to basically
make you
exactly like me and make me exactly like
you and then our discourse will be in
perfect secret we're both mutually
predictable and our joint free energy
will fall
so it's all about finding harmony in
groups and
a shared narrative a common ground um
and from that you can spin up all sorts
of hermeneutic interpretations and
indeed
you know the the imperatives for for
language in terms of
cultural niche construction under this
sort of variational
variational frameworks and and that that
would have been our third lecture which
i
which you can't do everything in half an
hour
certainly can't thank you so much
professor fristen on behalf of all the
participants here for uh for a
fascinating and
thought-provoking presentation